https://www.houseofhorrors.com/privacy

Privacy Policy of houseofhorrors.com - House of horrors
Ed GeinHenry LucasLucio FulciTexasThe ShiningThe VaultMovie NewsMoviesBengali MoviesBhojpuri MoviesBollywood MoviesGujarati MoviesHollywood MoviesKannada MoviesMalayalam MoviesMarathi MoviesPunjabi MoviesTamil MoviesTelugu Movies
Search
House of horrors Ed GeinHenry LucasLucio FulciTexasThe ShiningThe VaultMovie NewsMoviesBengali MoviesBhojpuri MoviesBollywood MoviesGujarati MoviesHollywood MoviesKannada MoviesMalayalam MoviesMarathi MoviesPunjabi MoviesTamil MoviesTelugu MoviesHome
Privacy Policy of houseofhorrors.com Privacy Policy of houseofhorrors.comHouseofhorrors.com Privacy PolicyThis privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their ‘Personally identifiable information’ (PII) is being used online. PII, as used in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app? We do not collect information from visitors of our site.When do we collect information in houseofhorrors.com?We collect information from you when you or enter information on our site.How do we use your information at houseofhorrors.com?We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:How do we protect visitor information?Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible.We use regular Malware Scanning.Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.We implement a variety of security measures when a user enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information.All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers.Do we use ‘cookies’?Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site’s or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.We use cookies to: Keep track of advertisements.Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third party services that track this information on our behalf.You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser’s Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.If you disable cookies off, some features will be disabled It won’t affect the users experience that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly.However, you can still place orders .Third Party DisclosureWe do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless we provide you with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property, or safety.However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.Third party linksOccasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.Google AdvertisingGoogle’s advertising requirements can be summed up by Google’s Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=enWe use Google AdSense Advertising on our website.Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.We have implemented the following: Remarketing with Google AdSenseGoogle Display Network Impression ReportingDemographics and Interests ReportingDoubleClick Platform IntegrationWe along with third-party vendors, such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions, and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.Opting out: Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising initiative opt out page or permanently using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.California Online Privacy Protection ActCalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law’s reach stretches well beyond California to require a person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting personally identifiable information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals with whom it is being shared, and to comply with this policy. – See more at: https://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpufAccording to CalOPPA we agree to the following: Users can visit our site anonymouslyOnce this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page, or as a minimum on the first significant page after entering our website.Our Privacy Policy link includes the word ‘Privacy’, and can be easily be found on the page specified above.Users will be notified of any privacy policy changes:On our Privacy Policy PageUsers are able to change their personal information:By logging in to their accountHow does our site handle do not track signals?We honor do not track signals and do not track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.Does our site allow third party behavioral tracking?It’s also important to note that we allow third party behavioral trackingCOPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, the nation’s consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children’s privacy and safety online.We do not specifically market to children under 13.Fair Information PracticesThe Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur: We will notify the users via email within 7 business daysWe will notify the users via in site notificationWe also agree to the individual redress principle, which requires that individuals have a right to pursue legally enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or a government agency to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.CAN SPAM ActThe CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.We collect your email address in order to:Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original transaction has occurredTo be in accordance with CANSPAM we agree to the following: NOT use false, or misleading subjects or email addressesIdentify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable wayInclude the physical address of our business or site headquartersMonitor third party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quicklyAllow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each emailIf at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us atFollow the instructions at the bottom of each email.And we will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence.Contacting Us at srini@digi1.coTop Horror Movies List Top Horror Movies ListDifferent Types of House of HorrorsBest Scariest Horror MoviesBest Horror Movies on HuluEpic Horror MoviesBest Horror Movies on NetflixTop Psychological Horror MoviesTop Horror Comedy moviesTop Underrated Horror MoviesTop PG-13 Horror MoviesTop Christmas Horror MoviesTop Cosmic and Space Horror MoviesTop Japanese Horror MoviesTop Korean Horror MoviesBest Horror Movies Streaming on Prime Video  Year Wise Horror Movies Year Wise Horror Movies ListBest Horror Movies of 2010Best Horror Movies of 2011The Best Horror Films of the 1990sBest Horror Movies of 2016Best Horror Movies of 2017Best Horror Movies of 2018Top Horror Movies of the 1980sBest Horror Movies of 2019Horror Movies Review 2006Horror Movies DVD Review 2008Horror Movie Dvd Review 2007 ABOUT USWelcome, all to the House of Horrors. Your first and last stop on the WWW (World Weird Web) of horror. We hope your stay here is a pleasant one as your trek through the blood-splattered halls of the House. Your dedicated host, the Caretaker, will serve as your guide leading you down a path of horror enlightenment. He has filled these hallowed rooms with all you will need to help in feeding your addiction to gore. The works of Fulci, Romero, Raimi, Carpenter, Savini, Karloff, Lugosi, Chaney, Argento, Barker, Hooper, Craven, ed gein and many others flow tirelessly across this landscape touching your dark soul and the genre you love.Contact us: srini@digi1.coFOLLOW US
T & CPrivacy PolicyAbout usAdvertise with usContact usGenres © 2019, HouseOfHorrors.com
Edit with Live CSS
SaveWrite CSS OR LESS and hit save. CTRL + SPACE for auto-complete.
